Utilizing otherworlders is a designated taboo.
Using the human body as material is also taboo.
Now that you have committed these offenses...
I must kill you.
Flare's successor, Flarette...
The blank white material you once were
has become so much like that girl.
I've waited eagerly these past ten
years for you to grow into your own.
All the while conducting repeated
experiments on erasing personalities.
Oh, that's right.
One time, I went too far and blanched
part of the Pure Concept itself,
which was quite the disaster.
But you know about that all too well.
I'm talking about the time an otherworlder's powers
turned a makeshift [White] and wiped out an entire town.
Flare was the only one...
Who suspected me at the time.
You... did that?
Are you surprised?
You poor thing,
the girl who failed to share the fate of her hometown.
Episode 6:
[Regression: Memories, Soul, Spirit]
Hey, Momo! What is this thing?! How do I kill it?
Who knows?
I assume it has something to do with original sin,
but if you can't defeat it why don't you just let it kill you?
I have to hurry and get to Menou!
Don't worry, Otherworlder. You'll soon forget everything.
No...
I don't want that...
Menou!
Auto Etheric Connect
(Conditions: Met)-
Improper Attachment, Pure Concept [Time]-
Unlock [Regression: Memories, Soul, Spirit]
This place...
Oh, right. It's the cathedral in Garm!
Why you...
Whoa!
This is my present from Menou!
I don't manage to get this that often.
I'm warning you to stay still!
Do you want to experience more pain?!
Then this is where I resist.
Etheric Connect
I'm sorry.
I have no intention of going with
anyone other than Menou...
But more importantly,
I absolutely refuse to let anyone but Menou kill me.
No good, huh? It's still moving.
I've never been able to stop this thing,
no matter how many times I try.
I wonder why?
I guess I don't have to rewind things this Time,
unlike back on the train.
I guess the best thing to do is
have that girl wreak havoc?
Etheric Connect-Improper
Attachment, Pure Concept [Time]-
Double Invoke [Teleportation, Weathering]
Is this a little mean?
But it's not really fair that she gets to have those ribbons.
Sorry, Momo.
Okay, time to do my thing again.
It's okay. I'll leave a sense of déjà vu, as usual.
And my love for Menou, of course.
So there's nothing to be scared of.
Wasn't I in a really bad situation?
Well, whatever. I guess I managed to get out of it.
Good grief. This is getting nowhere.
Barrier
What a pathetic flame!
The barrier my robe provides is more than enough.
Momo!
I guess that killed her.
Why? Why...?!
I swear I protected them!
So how...
Momo...
This... isn't fair...
No, no, noooo!!
I got them... from Menou...
They're the world's most precious...
Were the more precious...!
You'll pay for this!
Die, die, die, die! Just die!
How dare you...! It's all your fault!
Wh-what's this?!
Momo! Not the earthen vein?!
You can't, the entire castle will crumble on our heads!
Shut up, keep out of this!
Go die!
I hate everyone! Except Menou.
I love everything about her!
So you'll pay for this! I swear. I swear!
I hate you all! So much!
Except for Menou, you can all just die!
Wow Momo, you really went all out!
I was wrong to hold back to preserve the castle.
It's a den of corruption, anyway.
Allow me to go full force on this thing.
Stand back, riff-raff! I can't promise you won't get hurt!
Now then, demon.
Surely even you will die if I reduce you to nothing.
Slashing through history is enthralling indeed!
You're not being very aggressive, Ms. Menou.
You're quite adept at controlling ether
but don't have much of it, do you?
You'll eventually run out. What do you plan to do?
She separated me from Menou,
and made these stupid things attack me...
It's all... all because of...
Primary Red Gem
Primary Pseudo-concept
[Red]-Invoke [False Sun]
All because of that!
I'll eliminate you!
Someone broke the barrier?!
You know, if there's one thing I can brag about...
It's my aide.
She's the world's most competent-
Menou!
I'm so glad you're safe!
If anything happened to you, Menou...
What the hell did you come here for, you dummy?!
Why are you angry, Menou?
Didn't I tell you to run?!
I couldn't just leave you behind! I did the right thing!
How did that girl get away?!
Will you just shut up?!
Wait, what are you doing, Menou?!
What just happened?!
Did you just hear something that sounded like crying?
Do you hear that awful sound?!
Very competent, indeed, with copious amounts of ether.
But at this rate, she'll wear herself out before long.
I should still take care of you first, Ms. Menou.
Honestly...
Akari, why would you come when you
know it's going to be dangerous?
Well, because the safest place I know in
this world is right by your side, Menou.
You're such an idiot. But it's fine.
You've given me an idea.
Invoke
[Bubble]
You and your diversions. Just like Flare.
Did you intend to use the dregs of [Red]
left behind with what little ether you have?
Very predictable.
I suppose.
But this is what I'm really after!
I can't let my guard down for a second.
It seems I should put an end to this now.
Flare?!
How?
Don't tell me it was you disguised
as Ms. Menou all along,
so that you could approach me?!
You're right, I do love using diversions.
Menou?!
Etheric camouflage!
Akari! I'm going to borrow your ether!
Invoke
[Gale]
You have nothing protecting you now!
Thank goodness I'm the archbishop!
The magecraft built into this cathedral protected me!
An automatic system to guard dignitaries...!
You were so close, Ms. Menou.
Now this is really it for you!
I'm out of options.
Except for the most dangerous one,
the one I most wanted to avoid...
I have to use more than just Akari's ether,
but her Pure Concept itself,
and dive deep into her consciousness to do so...
Even if it's strictly forbidden, I have to!
Menou...?
It's swallowing me in...
Where... am I?
When is it?
I failed to become a villain.
A part of me never stopped longing to be a
priestess who was simply pure, just, and strong.
Even though my life has only ever had
meaning on this dark red path I'm on.
If I die now, can I go to that classroom over there?
Don't worry.
No matter what happens.
No matter who does what,
and whatever Time it might be...
I'll always be your best friend, Menou.
Akari?
You're right. Thanks, Akari!
Etheric Connect-Akari Tokitou,
Pure Concept [Time]-Invoke [Aging]
Wh... why...?
I'm different from you.
I helped so many people... so I deserve to live...
Archbishop Orwell.
With such strong desire,
why didn't you use your scripture?
Because I believed...
That if I cast aside all that was just and pure,
I would find my own path to follow...
Meaning I never found in my life
where I was nothing but righteous...
Tell me, Ms. Menou.
Your life has been the polar opposite of mine.
Do you have an answer?
I don't.
I've...
From the very beginning, I've-
You've worn yourself out after your little rampage, hmm?
I quite enjoyed fighting alongside you, Momo.
A dragon and a demon suddenly
emerged from underground,
and the Princess Knight Ashuna Grisarika
defeated them with the help of a priestess.
In the midst of it all,
Archbishop Orwell was killed in battle.
That was the story told to the public.
The archbishop's heretical crimes have been
concealed by the Church's higher ups,
never to be uncovered again, I imagine.
I-I'm so sorry, Menou.
What do you mean, Momo?
Um, the ribbons you gave me...
Th-they burned away...
When they were a gift from you I treasured
more than anything in the world...
Momo, turn around and close your eyes.
You look cute, Momo.
Menou...
How do you always give me what
I want when I need it most?
Who knows?
Because I'm your mentor, perhaps?
I love you so much!
The only person I love in the whole wide world is you!
I think Akari must have regressed back from
a future far beyond this point in time.
But even though she forgot
everything from before she regressed,
her affection for me remained somehow.
So you think that's why the girl
trusted you from the beginning?
Probably.
That's what I sensed when I made contact with
the depths of her soul and consciousness.
My future self managed to deceive
Akari so well to earn that much trust,
but I must have failed to kill her for some
reason and allowed her to regress back.
So I've made up my mind.
I'm going to keep going on this journey with Akari,
in order to find a way to kill her.
No, Menou...
No... No!
Menou!
What is it, Akari?
You're finally up?
Akari?
Menou!
What's wrong?
I just... had a nightmare.
A nightmare? What kind?
I don't know.
I don't know, but I love you so much, Menou.
Fine, fine. You're very welcome.
I'm sorry.
You should know...
I was trying to kill you.
That would have been fine.
You should have just killed me!
No way. Not when I finally learned... what friendship is.
No, Menou!
Menou...!
No. If this is how things end...
If I'm going to be killed by the likes of her,
I wanted Menou to kill me instead.
So long, you incomplete concept of Time.
So please, make sure you kill me properly this time...
Menou.
Next Episode
Port City of Libelle
Next episode: Port City of Libelle.